ALES Records 5225
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Dayton, Ohio, re formation of local committee for Wisconsin and BMSS, Frances Benning, 1930-1932 (Box 9, Folder 65)
- Toledo, Ohio, reports of Elsabelle Goss, YWCft Industrial Secretary, 1930-1932 (Box 9, Folder 66)
- Toledo, Ohio, reports of Elsabelle Goss, YWCft Industrial Secretary, 1930-1932 (Box 9, Folder 67)
- Cleveland, Ohio, Ohio women plan luncheon for Mary Anderson and invite Blacks, 1929-1930 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  correspondents include Margaret Bourke White, C. Gehrine, E. Magee
- Cincinnati, Ohio re Clothing Institute, and with Vera Woods, Industrial Secretary, 1930-1931 (Box 9, Folder 69)
- Cincinnati, Ohio re Clothing Institute, and with Vera Woods, Industrial Secretary, 1930-1931 (Box 9, Folder 70)
- Columbus, Ohio, re cooperation of ASW and AFL, Alma Herbst, 1929-1930 (Box 9, Folder 71)
- Toledo, Ohio re cooperation of YWCA and ASW, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 72)
- Pennsylvania District, local committees in Reading, Chester, Wilkes Barre, and Turtle Point, 1930-1932 (Box 9, Folder 73)
- Pennsylvania District, local committees in Reading, Chester, Wilkes Barre, and Turtle Point, 1930-1932 (Box 9, Folder 74)
- Philadelphia, Pa., Pennsylvania District, 1930-1931 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  classes of Hosiery Workers, plans for WTUL conference to be held at BMSS, with Alice Liveright re: Elizabeth Moffat's thesis, publications of Educational Dept. sent to M. Carey Thomas
- Philadelphia, Pa., Pennsylvania District, 1930-1932 (Box 9, Folder 76)
- Philadelphia, Pa., Pennsylvania District, 1930-1932 (Box 9, Folder 77)
- Philadelphia, Pa., Pennsylvania District, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  community activities of former SS students, performances by Hedgerow "Little Theatre," J. Edelman of Textiles Workers' Union about summer
- Pittsburgh, plans for SS alumnae to study conditions in industry, reports of local classes, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 79)
- Durham, N. C., Louise L. McLaren and Helen Mulvaney of SSS, invitation to conference of liberals at SSS, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 80)
- Maryland-Southern Summer School, program for joint BMSS and SSS conference at Winston Salem, 1931-1932 (Box 9, Folder 81)
- Louisville, Ky., 1929-1930 (Box 9, Folder 82)
- North Carolina, program for workers' education conference, Winston Salem, "Remedies for Unemployment", 1932 (Box 9, Folder 83)
- Virginia, to Mathilda Lindsey re recruiting, 1930-1931 (Box 9, Folder 84)
- North Carolina, 1930-1931 (Box 9, Folder 85)
- Washington, D.C., 1930 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  Mary Anderson, Director of Woman's Bureau and chairman of SS committees for Southern region, H. H. Broach, President IBEW (AFL), Alice Cheyney, International Labor Office, J. P. Frey, President Metal Trades (AFL), and Linna E. Bresette
- Washington, D.C., 1930 (Box 9, Folder 87)
- Southern District, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  University of Virginia Extension Dept. offers to contact SS alumnae res further study, John Hope, President of Atlanta University res talk by HWS, application of Black student Zuline Bush, Gladys E. Palmer re: job history questionnaires
- District of Columbia, 1930-1932 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  Mary Anderson re publishing job histories, Elizabeth Christman (President of WTUL), and Ben Marsh, People's Lobby
- District of Columbia, 1930-1932 (Box 9, Folder 90)
- Wisconsin Summer School, Alice Shoemaker, Executive Secretary of WSS, about the session, 1930-1932 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  also minutes of Advisory committee and annual reports
- Wisconsin Summer School, Alice Shoemaker, Executive Secretary of WSS, about the session, 1930-1932 (Box 9, Folder 92)
- WSS, John A. Connors and Russel Baulder, Economics, text used at WSS, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 93)
- Wisconsin District, 1930-1931 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  Alice Shoemaker re WSS and program of Institute and brochure of WSS, report from Coit and Alma Herbst to Ohio committee
- Far West District, 1932-1933 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  Miriam Bonner about local classes in Los Angeles, strike of ILGWU workers, Ethel Clark re: participation of workers in Denver Labor Day Parade, Alice Henry
- Middle West District, 1932-1933 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  Polly Hoover from Indianapolis, Commonwealth College, Mena Ark, Harold Coy re: Unemployed Citizens' League in St. Louis, to Kathleen Jennison Lowrie re: Smith's new job as Supervisor of Work Relief under the WPA in Washington, and Coit's new responsibilities in the ASW, Dorothea Nordholt and the Community Institute in Indianapolis, Helen Swoyer of YWCA, and Helen Weber re: drama classes in Michigan
- Chicago, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  Florence Curtis Hanson re: recruiting teachers in workers education from the Teachers Union, proposed study of SS students' activities in follow-up study by Mildred Price
- Connecticut, Bridgeport, re conference on "Where is the Depression Leading?", 1932 (Box 9, Folder 98)
- Hartford, Conn., Study of NRA minimum wage plan in local classes, New England Workers' education conference, 1932-1933 (Box 9, Folder 99)
  suggestion of speakers
- Boston, Mass., Rose Andelman, Constance Williams re: local classes, 1932-1933 (Box 9, Folder 100)
- Holyoke, Mass, Mary Murdock re class on unemployment insurance, labor plays recommended, 1931-1932 (Box 9, Folder 101)
- Lawrence, Mass., President, Central Labor Union re: plan, 1931-1933 (Box 9, Folder 102)
- New Bedford, Mass., 1932-1933 (Box 9, Folder 103)
  A. Hodson on work of Mew England Alumnae Association, study plans, Sarah Burgess requests funds through Works Relief Organization for Workers' classes, Miriam Fuhrman re new YWCA summer school, successful lectures reported by WTUL, New Bedford
- Northampton, Mass., 1933 (Box 9, Folder 104)
  ASW schools in the Connecticut Valley, Eleanor Ernst to Halo Chadwick re: industrial study groups on minimum wage law
- Lowell, Mass., application, conditions in shoe shops, 1932-1933 (Box 9, Folder 105)
- Springfield, Mass., Eileen O'Connor re: discussion group, for workers, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 106)
- Wellesley College, Mass., re: study materials, 1931-1932 (Box 9, Folder 107)
- Pawtucket, R. I., 1931-1932 (Box 9, Folder 108)
  re: numerous projects in Woonsocket, and Pawtucket in Workers' education, class in labor dramatics taught by Hollace Ransdell, and cooperative programs shared by YWCA, ASW, WTUL and Consumers' League
- Providence, R. I., recruiting and classes led by Annie King, 1931-1932 (Box 9, Folder 109)
- Pawtucket, R. I., drama project and WTUL chapter proposed by Francis Gorman of United Textile Workers' Union, 1931-1932 (Box 9, Folder 110)
- New York City, 1932-1933 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  Lucy Mason invited to speak on Industrial Recovery Act, request to Coit to suggest names of members of Wage Boards, League for Industrial Democracy appeals for strikers' relief, Fenner Brockway's schedule, League of Nations Association pamphlets on Disarmament, request to E.G. Lindeman, New York School of Social Work to encourage students to write theses on ASW data, Raymond V. Mood, Director of Reading Labor College and plan for cooperative teaching project, Workers Education Bureau's display for the convention of AFL on workers' education
- Niagara Falls, with YWCA secretaries, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 112)
- Rochester, N. Y., Effie Riley and Jean Carter, 1932-1933 (Box 9, Folder 113)
- Syracuse, N. Y., Consumers' League and ASW organize first commission to study laundry industry, 1932-1933 (Box 9, Folder 114)
- Brookwood, Katonah, N. Y. (Box 9, Folder 115)
- Columbus, Ohio, names of SS alumnae to Ohio State Relief Commissioner to assist planning for FERA classes, 1932-1933 (Box 9, Folder 116)
- Harrisburg, local classes, 1931-1932 (Box 9, Folder 117)
- Philadelphia, and Pittsburgh, local classes, 1932-1933 (Box 9, Folder 118)
- Philadelphia, and Pittsburgh, local classes, 1932-1933 (Box 9, Folder 119)
- Wilkes Barre Scranton district, local classes, 1932-1933 (Box 9, Folder 120)
- Maryland, Workers' education in Baltimore, cooperation between unions, Goucher College and YWCA, 1932-1933 (Box 9, Folder 121)
- Southern Summer School, Louise Leonard McLaren and Helen Mulvaney (Box 9, Folder 122)
- Southern Summer School, Louise McLaren, Director of SSW describes spirit of times, 1932-1933 (Box 9, Folder 123)
  depression and problems faced by workers
- Virginia, Mrs. Ralph Clapfield, drama teacher to unemployed workers, 1932-1933 (Box 9, Folder 124)
- Wisconsin Summer School, publications, articles on WSS, Social Science workshop at WSS, 1932-1933 (Box 9, Folder 125)
- Writings of former students of SS, various topics (Box 9, Folder 126)
- Student autobiographies, WSS, mimeographed, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 127)
- SSWW, student autobiographies, tss. (Box 9, Folder 128)
- A (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Alumnae Association of Barnard Summer School (BSS) and BMSS, 1928-1929 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Alumnae Association of Barnard Summer School (BSS) and BMSS, 1928-1930 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Alumnae Association of Barnard Summer School (BSS) and BMSS, 1928-1931 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Alumnae Association of Barnard Summer School (BSS) and BMSS, 1928-1931 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Alumnae Association for Adult Education, 1927-1932 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Alumnae Association for Adult Education, 1927-1932 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Alumnae Association for Adult Education, 1927-1932 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- American Federation of Labor (Box 10, Folder 9)
- American Federation of Labor (Box 10, Folder 10)
- American Federation of Labor, 1928-1931 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Ahlers, Harriet (of the American Association of University Women) (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Anderson, Mary, 1928-1932 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Anderson, Mary, 1928-1932 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Anderson, Mary, 1928-1932 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Andrews, Dr. Katherine, 1930-1931 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Antioch College, 1929-1930 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Applicants, correspondence re: students, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Applications by faculty, 1931-1932 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Art Workshop for Industrial and College Women, 1928-1932 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  directed by Mabel Leslie offered classes in visual and performing arts (dance, drama) and creative arts
- Art Workshop for Industrial and College Women, 1928-1932 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Art Workshop for Industrial and College Women, 1928-1932 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Art Workshop for Industrial and College Women, 1928-1932 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Art Workshop for Industrial and College Women, 1928-1932 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- B (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Ballots for Joint Adminstration Committee, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- (BSS,) reports, applicants, fliers, 1927-1932 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- (BSS,) reports, applicants, fliers, 1927-1932 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- BSS, faculty reports, 1930-1932 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- BSS, sessions, 1931-1932 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- BSS, sessions, 1931-1932 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- BSS, sessions, 1931-1931 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- BSS, finance appeals, 1931-1930 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- BSS, finance appeals, 1931-1929 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- BSS, finance appeals, 1931-1928 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- BSS, finance appeals, 1931-1927 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- BSS, finance appeals, 1931-1926 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- BSS, with Columbia University (Box 10, Folder 38)
- BSS, additional scholarships, 1931-1932 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- BSS, with Barnard College undergraduates, 1931-1932 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- BSS, publicity, 1931-1932 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- BSS, speakers, 1931-1932 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- BSS, with Barnard College, 1932-1933 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Berea College, 1929-1930 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Biddle, Ruth, 1928-1929 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Biemiller, Andrew, 1930-1931 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Black, Eleanor Goldmark, 1930-1931 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Br (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Brannon, Lida, 1928-1929 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Brookwood, with A. J. Muste et al., conferences, programs, fliers, 1927-1932 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Brookwood, with A. J. Muste et al., conferences, programs, fliers, 1927-1932 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Brookwood, with A. J. Muste et al., conferences, programs, fliers, 1927-1932 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Brookwood, with A. J. Muste et al., conferences, programs, fliers, 1927-1932 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- BMSS, Books and session outlines, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 54)
- BMSS, Class and council minutes, report on physical education, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- BMSS, M. Carey Thomas sends financial support despite hard economic times, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 56)
- BMSS, tea, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 57)
- BMSS, weekend conference (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Bu (Box 10, Folder 59)
- Camp, Sophie, 1930-1931 (Box 10, Folder 60)
- Canadian district, scholarships, 1929-1930 (Box 10, Folder 61)
- Caples, Anna, Vassar College, 1931-1932 (Box 10, Folder 62)
- Carter, Jean, application as instructor (Box 10, Folder 63)
- Ch (Box 10, Folder 64)
- Chadwick, Halo (Box 10, Folder 65)
- Chicago District, 1928-1931 (Box 10, Folder 66)
- Chicago District, 1928-1931 (Box 10, Folder 67)
- Chicago District, 1928-1931 (Box 10, Folder 68)
- Christenson, Edith, application as instructor (Box 10, Folder 69)
- Clark, Helen, application as instructor (Box 10, Folder 70)
- Clippings re: Summer schools, 1930-1931 (Box 10, Folder 71)
- Co (Box 10, Folder 72)
- Coit, Eleanor mostly with Hilda W. Smith, 1928-1932 (Box 10, Folder 73)
- Colby, Josephine, 1928-1932 (Box 10, Folder 74)
- Coldwell, Laura, 1930-1931 (Box 10, Folder 75)
- Collins, Caroline Chadwick, 1928-1931 (Box 10, Folder 76)
- Collins, Caroline Chadwick, 1928-1931 (Box 10, Folder 77)
- Columbia University, 1928-1932 (Box 10, Folder 78)
- Columbia University, 1928-1932 (Box 10, Folder 79)
- Columbia University, 1928-1932 (Box 10, Folder 80)
- Columbia University, 1928-1932 (Box 10, Folder 81)
- Columbia University: Committee on Workers Classes, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 82)
- Comstock, Ada Louise, 1928-1931 (Box 10, Folder 83)
- Constitution (Box 10, Folder 84)
- Conferences of southern alumnae of BMMS and SSS, 1925-1934 (Box 10, Folder 85)
- Conferences of SSS, 1928-1932 (Box 10, Folder 86)
- Conference, Winston Salem, N. C., 1937 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  January
- D (Box 11, Folder 1)
- District chairmen, reports including Mary Anderson, 1928-1929 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Reports to district chairmen re BMSS students, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- District lists of BMSS students, 1928-1932 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- District lists of BMSS students, 1928-1932 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Detroit district, correspondence, 1929-1931 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- E (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Educational Council, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Educational Committee, 1929-1930 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Educational Department, reports and correspondence, 1930-1932 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Educational Department, reports and correspondence, 1930-1932 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Educational Department, reports and correspondence, 1930-1932 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Educational Department, finance, 1929-1934 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  includes funding from Julius Rosenwald Fund, budget, other fund correspondence, and financial acknowledgements
- Educational Department, finance, 1929-1934 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Educational Department, finance, 1929-1934 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Educational Department, finance, 1929-1934 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Educational Department, finance, 1929-1934 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Educational Department, finance, 1929-1934 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Edwards, Corwin D., 1928-1929 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Employers Association (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Engagements of Hilda W. Smith, 1930-1931 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Expense account sheets, 1930-1931 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- F (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Faculty applications and correspondence, 1928-1932 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Faculty applications and correspondence, 1928-1932 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Faculty applications and correspondence, 1928-1932 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Faculty applications and correspondence, 1928-1932 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Faculty applications and correspondence, 1928-1932 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Faculty applications and correspondence, 1928-1932 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Faculty fundraising (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Far West District, recruiting and reports, 1928-1935 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Far West District, recruiting and reports, 1928-1935 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Far West Cities: students' records (Box 11, Folder 33)
- G (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Givens, Meredith B., 1928 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Gogorza, Mrs. Maitland De, 1930-1931 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Gold, Theresa, 1929-1930 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Griffiths, Mary, 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- H, 1929-1932 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- H, 1929-1932 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- H, 1929-1932 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Hanson, Alice, 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Harley, Harrison, H., psychologist, 1928-1929 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Harris, Eileen S. (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Hawk, Brace, 1930-1931 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Hecht, Rosa Pringle and Zoltan Hecht, 1929-1930 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  includes fliers re craft workshops in Saluda N.C., also project to help striking textile workers
- Herrman, Helen includes study of district Workers', 1927-1929 (Box 11, Folder 47)
- Hewes, Amy includes reports on recruiting foreign students in Russia and Germany, 1927-1932 (Box 11, Folder 48)
- Hohman, Helen Fisher, relations with the Chicago District Committee, 1927-1929 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- I, incorporation certificate of the Women's Scholarship Fund (Box 11, Folder 50)
- Indianapolis District, 1929-1930 (Box 11, Folder 51)
- International Industrial Relations Association, with vice-president Mary Van Kleeck, 1929-1932 (Box 11, Folder 52)
- Inquiries, general, 1930-1932 (Box 11, Folder 53)
- Inquiries, general, 1930-1932 (Box 11, Folder 54)
- Joint Administrative Committee, reports of summer schools, 1928-1930 (Box 11, Folder 55)
- Joint Administrative Committee, reports of summer schools, 1928-1930 (Box 11, Folder 56)
- Joint Administrative Committee, reports of summer schools, 1928-1930 (Box 11, Folder 57)
- K (Box 11, Folder 58)
- Kingsbury, Dr. Susan, 1931-1932 (Box 11, Folder 59)
- Kohn, Lucile, 1931-1932 (Box 11, Folder 60)
- Koken, Mary, 1928-1931 (Box 11, Folder 61)
- L (Box 11, Folder 62)
- Labor conferences, 1929-1930 (Box 11, Folder 63)
- Labor papers (Box 11, Folder 64)
- Labor Press (Photographs removed to photograph file) (Box 11, Folder 65)
- Le (Box 11, Folder 66)
- Lindsay, Matilda, 1929-1930 (Box 11, Folder 67)
- Lists, 1929-1930 (Box 11, Folder 68)
- Luncheon for BMSS, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 69)
- M (Box 11, Folder 70)
  includes memorandum re BMSS and other summer schools describing "pro-labor slant" of the schools, n.d. correspondence with Dr. Marion Manter re health at BMSS, also Smith to Miss Maley discussing future developments in Workers' education
- Macy Foundation, 1930-1931 (Box 11, Folder 71)
- Mrs. Maclay, contributors' lists, 1927-1929 (Box 11, Folder 72)
- Me (Box 11, Folder 73)
- Merrill, Phyllis, organizing and teaching classes for workers, 1930-1931 (Box 11, Folder 74)
- Middle West, BMSS students, 1931-1932 (Box 11, Folder 75)
- Middle West, BMSS students, rejects, withdrawals, 1930-1939 (Box 11, Folder 76)
- Middle West, Chicago, 1929-1932 (Box 11, Folder 77)
- Middle West, Chicago, 1929-1932 (Box 11, Folder 78)
- Middle West, Indianapolis, 1931-1932 (Box 11, Folder 79)
- Middle West, Michigan with Katherine J. Lowrie re field trip, 1931-1932 (Box 11, Folder 80)
- Middle West, Ohio (Box 11, Folder 81)
- Middle West, St. Louis (Box 11, Folder 82)
- Mil (Box 11, Folder 83)
- N, includes proposal for "A Chain of Peoples Colleges" (Box 12, Folder 1)
- New England District, 1927-1932 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- New England District, 1927-1932 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- New England District, 1927-1932 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- New England District, 1927-1932 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- New England District, 1927-1932 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- New England District, 1927-1932 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- New England District, 1927-1932 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- New England District, 1927-1932 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- New England District, 1927-1932 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- New Jersey District, 1929-1930 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  correspondents include Smith, Elizabeth Hiss (YWCA), Teresa Ludwig and Coit who describes the functions of the Educational Secretary
- New Jersey District, 1929-1930 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- New Jersey District, 1929-1930 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- New York district, 1929-1930 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- New York city, appeal for Vineyard Shore School (VSS), 1931-1932 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- New York city, BMSS students, 1931-1932 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- New York State, BMSS students, 1931-1932 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- New York State, 1931-1932 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- New York Alumnae Association, 1931-1932 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Republication of "A Prayer" by Ruth Collins on change in her attitude to Black workers (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Ohio District re field trip and health of BMSS student (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Ohio District re field trip and health of BMSS student (Box 12, Folder 22)
- P (Box 12, Folder 23)
  Mildred Price re her M. A. thesis, benefit performance of "Parsifal" for summer schools, and note from Frances Perkins
- Palmer, Gertrude, application as instructor and correspondence re economics course, 1927-1931 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Park, Marion Edwards (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Pennsylvania District, 1929-1932 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  Eleanor Lansing Dulles, alumnae bulletins, lists of Pennsylvania students at BMSS
- Pennsylvania District, 1929-1932 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Pennsylvania District, 1929-1932 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Pennsylvania District, 1929-1932 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Upstate Pennsylvania (Box 12, Folder 30)
  report on BMSS student, thanks to two firms and one union for financial support, note from Cornelia Bryce Pinchot
- Upstate Pennsylvania (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Philadelphia, lists and reports on BMSS students, 1930-1932 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Philadelphia, lists and reports on BMSS students, 1930-1932 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Pittsburgh, BMSS students, 1931-1932 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Pittsburgh, BMSS students, 1931-1932 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Pocono Peoples College, newsletter, 1929-1930 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Pioneer Youth of America, W. Walter Ludwig re: childrens' camps in West Virginia (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Publicity, articles and lists, 1927-1931 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Publicity, articles and lists, 1927-1931 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Publicity, articles and lists, 1927-1931 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Publicity, articles and lists, 1927-1931 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Q (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Raushenbush, Stephen, Economics instructor, 1930-1931 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Recommendations from faculty, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- References, bibliography, 1929-1930 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Reports on BMSS, 1928-1929 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Report on proposed summer school for office workers, 1928-1929 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Reports on BMSS students, 1920-1921 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Sassaman, Walter re: men's summer school, 1930-1931 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Schepp foundation: scholarships, 1928-1929 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Schneiderman, Rose re: 25th anniversary of the Women's Trade Union League (Box 12, Folder 51)
- Seattle Committee, scholarships, 1928-1929 (Box 12, Folder 52)
- Sells, Dr. Dorothys faculty application, 1930-1931 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- Smith, Ethel, labor representative at BMSS, with labor press and various speakers, 1929-1930 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  describes her work of informing BMSS non-union students about the labor Movement, study of workers' education for the National YWCA
- Smith, Ethel, labor representative at BMSS, with labor press and various speakers, 1929-1930 (Box 12, Folder 55)
- Hilda W. Smith, articles re BMSS, 1922-1931 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  also includes articles by Mary Van Kleeck, Jack Herling, M. Carey Thomas, and Margaret Hill Collins
- Hilda W. Smith, articles re BMSS, 1922-1931 (Box 12, Folder 57)
- Hilda W. Smith, articles re BMSS, 1922-1931 (Box 12, Folder 58)
- Smith with Armstrong Association res Black women in industry, 1931-1932 (Box 12, Folder 59)